I think everyone's motivation is getting higher.
We're going to have a big rally today, but until we get there...
Since we are going to perform on the main stage
I'm sure each member was anxious at first.
I wondered how it would be like.
But we had a strategy meeting.
We had strategy meetings with each other and with the staff and myself, and as we went along
As we went along, I was more and more motivated from anxiety to motivation, and now I'm very motivated.
I think I'm full of motivation.
I'm going to ask Kanda Meiji to buy this for me.
I'm going to go to Kanda Meiji now to ask them for a favor.
Please take a look. This guy is saying "DODO" to something he doesn't want to regret.
And he's writing "Can-Chu" here like a bunny, so much so that he's saying to this person, "Can-Chu, don't regret it.
Kanda Myojin is the god of victory? It's like there is a god of victory.
I celebrate all my auditions and exams here, and I pass all of them.
I come to Kanda Myojin every year.
I ask for favors.
I come to Kanda Myojin.
Seino!
Yay!
So cute!
I'll be praying for you all my life.
I'll be praying for you.
I know it's scary, but I feel like we've come a long way since we were all headed in different directions.
I feel like we're all heading in the same direction, even the fans.
I'm not so scared anymore.
If it were simple, I'd be scared of the real thing.
I wonder if this will make you guys more excited.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much!
No, no, no, no!
Fingers up!
It's kinda lame, isn't it?
I talked a lot with the members,
We did a project during the Golden Week holidays,
That's how we got through to the fans,
And that's how we got through to the fans, and they came out to see us,
I was very anxious at first, but I lost a lot of confidence,
I was much less anxious at the beginning.
Everyone around me created this environment for me,
I am very grateful for that.
That's why I want to do more,
But it is difficult. I still have the anxiety that it is difficult to know where to start,
Half of my anxiety disappeared from the beginning.
I am sure that once you see it, you will be hooked,
I'm your number one fan,
I think I'm your biggest fan,
I can confidently tell everyone that it's good,
I'm so proud to be a part of it,
It may sound like a dream, but..,
It may sound like a dream to be on the main stage at TIFF for the first time,
But I want to make this dream come true with everyone,
I think we can make it come true at Tenchu.
Hinata Kera of Menkara is with me.
Eeeeeeeeee ample pie!
I didn't think my intonation was that good,
I'll talk.
Really? Oh, yeah!
Maybe so.
Each of the seven of us has our own personality and cuteness,
They really don't have the same personality,
I'm sure that if you come to Candy Tune,
I can make an oshimen of any one of them.
But I think they are all too cute and too good to be true,
But there are still a lot of people who can't decide which one to choose because they think it's too cute or too good,
So, please come and visit us.
I am 172cm.
I originally wanted to be a model.
So I wanted to be tall, but I was short.
Don't mess with the skin.
I wanted to be pretty.
I was just tiny. Negative.
Maybe I'm a little relieved.
Huh?
We've got about three minutes.
Until the show?
Maybe.
What? No way.
What? No?
What?
I'm, uh, I'm gonna be gone for about a half an hour.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're gonna have a great time at the play. We're gonna have a great time at the play.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
CAR
Never The pretty girl may be in love with you
To my way To my way
It's me who asks the question
So dream, love, love, see, be careful, if you wait for everything
For the first time, we are Gummy Tune.
Pleased to meet you.
For me, TIFF is the place that made me want to become an idol,
And it is also the place where I wanted to be an idol because I wanted to be in TIFF,
TIFF is the place that made me want to become an idol because I wanted to be in TIFF, and also the place that made me fall in love with idols,
TIFF is really important to me,
I think that many idols have the same yearning for TIFF.
Candy Tune is only 5 months old,
If we can make it to the main stage, we will get a lot of attention from here,If we are able to stand on the main stage, we will be able to draw a lot of attention from here,
I am sure that we will be able to see a bigger stage ahead of us,
Even though we are still newborns, we definitely want to win here,
I would like to see the next view and accelerate the momentum of this competition,
I hope you will all give me your support.
This year is my fifth time to perform at TIFF,
This year will be my fifth time to perform at TIFF, but I have never been on the main stage before.
As an idol, I know how difficult it is to perform on the main stage.
I have been discussing and taking lessons every day with the members to improve the quality of our performance.
I definitely want to be on the main stage and be the main character of this summer.
Candy Tune will be my first idol show.
TIFF and summer festivals have been my favorite places,
I have always looked forward to these events from the audience as a fan just like you.
This year I will be performing on stage as an idol.
Every day since I became a Candy Tune has been like a dream come true...
I've been working so hard to make it all happen.
It's my first time to be an idol and to be on the main stage at my first TIFF...
I think it's like a dream come true.
Please let us dream big once more this summer!
Candy Tune has a sense of polymorphism
I think Candy Tune is a fun and bright group.
I think we are a fun and cheerful group.
We are going to compete on the main stage of TIFF this year
I'm looking forward to competing in the main stage of TIFF this year as Candy Tune.
There are many idols and idol groups in Japan.
There are many idols and idol groups in Japan, but only 8 of them are allowed to participate in this competition.
I'm sure there are many other idol groups that wanted to participate but couldn't.
I think there are many other idol groups that wanted to participate but couldn't. I'm very grateful that we, as a debutant, can be one of them.
I am very grateful to be a part of one of them.
I really want to win this competition, but I also want to do it in our own way.
I hope we will be able to fight together with everyone at Ame-chan in our own way
I hope we will be cheerful, happy, and smiling all the way to the end.
This will be our first summer with Candy Tune.
I hope you will laugh a lot and have a lot of fun.
I just want to say one thing right now
I'm very happy right now.
The reason why is because
I'm so happy that all of you Candy Tune members are here with me for all the TiFF awards competitions.
I'm so happy to see all of you candy people gathered together like this.
We are all working together in this same space.
to work hard for the competition for all the prizes
Just by having all of you here
I'm already happy enough now.
I'm so happy to see that you are tweeting and cheering me on more than I can imagine.
I'm so happy to see you tweeting and cheering for us every day.
I don't know.
It's hard not to feel
I can't help but feel that you are supporting me every day.
I really feel it and realize it.
I really feel the expectation and the support from the audience.
By standing on the main stage, I dream of standing on the main stage together
I believe that by standing on the main stage, we can make our dream of standing together on the main stage happy.
I believe that we can make this dream come true.
I would like to carry this happy feeling to the main stage
I would like to win it together with all of you.
I love you all so much!
I am more scared than any of the other members.
I'm more anxious than any of the other members.
When I heard about this competition for the TiFF main stage, I was very anxious and wondered if I could make it.
I was so anxious and wondered if I could handle it.
I was thinking about it a lot.
But as the shows went on and on...
I was thinking that I wanted to make the fans happy.
And when I saw tweets like "I want to put Canju on the main stage...
I thought that I could do my best.
I think I can do my best.
I really think that I can do my best every day.
So, I'm more positive than ever.
Let's make it to the main stage together!
Thank you very much for your support!
Let's do our best!
As the six of us have said so far
We all have our own thoughts and feelings.
How many times have you performed, Kiri?
I've been on the 5th show...
But we haven't been on the main stage yet...
or "This is my first time to perform at TiFF.
I'm sure each of us has our own thoughts and feelings.
But everyone wants to be a part of TiFF for themselves.
It's not that we want to be on the main stage of TiFF.
We want to be on the main stage for Candy Tune, a group that we love.
that we love so much, Candy Tune, to be on the main stage
We are dreaming to be on the main stage.
We are really good at what we do for other people.
For Candy Tune.
Then we can give this up too.
We really put our lives on the line for Candy Tune
We are all working hard for Candy Tune
So we are also working hard for Candy Tune
I'd like to see a wonderful stage for Candy Tune.
I hope that everyone in Candy Tune will join us on the main stage.
Candy Tune group on the main stage
and say "Yay!" with everyone.
I hope we can stand on the main stage and see the beautiful scenery together.
I hope we can see the beautiful scenery together.
Can you all lend me a hand?
Thank you very much. Our goal is to go from Harajuku to the world,
We will do our best every day to be an important step toward that goal. Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much for your continued support.We would very much appreciate your continued support.
Thank you very much.
How was everyone?
Yay!
Was it good?
Was it bad last time?
Yay!
Yes, it was a lot of fun.
Now, let's go to the photographer, shall we?
Yes, I'm asking for a photographer because of this.
Please.
Let's all go at once!
Oooh!
Se-no!
Congratulations, everyone.
Let's go!
If you had a meeting with us, you would have told us what you wanted to hear from our clients.
I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it.
If you're drinking water, congratulations.
I can't wait to hear it, and we'll all be together.
I want to hear it!
I don't know anything about it, but I'd like to ask for your congratulations.
I'll have the photographer hold it for you.
The photographer will bring it to you.
Photographer, please!
I'm going to the stage!
Oh, wow!
Yay!
Where did you get that?
I'm so, so, so surprised.
Why did you ench? Why would you die and still be enchanted?
Oh! Misao!
I've got something!
Smudge Sammy Sammy Sadie.
Yay!
I'll do my best.
Um...
Today is...
Isn't it a rally?
The skin main contest!
But...
On the surface...
"We're going to do our best.
But in reality, everyone's anxious, right?
That's why I'm wondering if there's anything we can do.
I've been thinking about it with my staff and everyone else.
We asked our fans to write messages of support
We asked fans to write messages of support.
It's a great puzzle!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
It's so big I can't open it anymore.
It's so big I can't open it with the size of my hands.
Hey, can I see it?
I can't look at it because I'll cry.
Oh, my God!
Well, actually, I was going to ask everyone to write this down during the benefit, but
But at this point, we've received a lot more letters than we thought we would.
I thought it would be a good time for everyone to see it, so I'm going to give it to you as a surprise present.
So I thought I'd give you a surprise present!
I'm going to give you a surprise gift at this time, such as these in-shoes, which are definitely an activity.
I love you, Nachiko!
He said, "Let's make this the best summer ever!
I'm not just saying that to make you happy.
Right...
You know, I'm sure everyone is anxious.
I'm sure everyone is anxious and the fans want everyone to be on the main stage, so...
So, let's stand on the main stage with high expectations!
One more thing.
Let's line up there.
Let's line up...
I think it was supposed to be an announcement.
I think we were going to make an announcement.
June?
They said they were going to announce June 27th.
Yes, but...
What a surprise!
Yesterday...
I made a toast!
Congratulations!
Yes, I did.
I don't have to work so hard to announce it anymore.
It says "no mouth" on it.
Oh, no mouth?
It says "no more mouths.
No more single mouthfuls.
And it's messy.
I think this is also due to everyone's hard work over the past two months,
I hope you can win the whole focus,
June 27th will be our first solo show,
I'm sure everyone here will be there.
Yay!
So please look forward to it!
Please do!
Three, two, one!
Thank you very much!
Okay, one more time. Candy Pose in three, two, one.
Three, two, one. Thank you very much, everybody.Thank you all.
Last but not least, I wanted to do the engine we always do for everyone.
This engine is for the TiFU2023 mainstery super-dudes competition.
I hope we can all get pumped up for the all-out victory.
Is that all right with you?
Yes, I was at the convenience store earlier, so I think we're all good.
It's true, we all did it earlier, so it's fine.
I don't have to explain it anymore, but I'll explain it one more time.
Thumbs and pinkies out.
Three times.
Three times, "I'm in great shape, I'm in great shape, I'm in great shape, I'm in great shape...
I'll give it to you in the following way.
The key is to smile at the end.
Okay, so...
Let's go!
Let's go for the TiFU main stage super-dudes!
On your game, on your game, on your game, on your game!
Yes!
Thank you!
That's all for now, we are Cute Tune!
Thank you very much!
The show is over!
Yes!
During the show, there was a surprise from the book.
I was so surprised!
I received a lot of love.
Thank you very much.
Another surprise was the big banner that MISA brought.
All the members couldn't stop crying, even though I cry easily.
I cried so much.
But I think the stage was really warm and warm,
It was thanks to all of you, so I was really happy.
The show is still a month away, so I hope we can all do our best.
I hope everyone will do their best.
Thank you very much.
Katsubo!